

Jemi Pankhania

SharePoint Developer/Designer

More than 2 years of extensive experience as a SharePoint Developer/Designer with a good grip on Customization & Branding using all the OOB features, JSOM/CSOM/SSOM/REST, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Jquery. I can design very user-friendly responsive SharePoint intranet portals & Business Process Automation Solutions on SharePoint.

+917359797359

Mumbai

in www.linkedin.com/in/jemi-pankhania

WORK EXPERIENCE

SharePoint Consultant RedexSoft Pvt Ltd.

06/2017 - Present

Gurgaon

Responsibilities

- Requirement analysis and designing solution on SharePoint
- Testing and Troubleshooting
- SharePoint Branding and Customization

Contact: Gaurav Agrawal - +917011483110

SharePoint Executive

Kalpataru Ltd. 🗹 02/2017 - 06/2017

Mumhai

Kalpataru Ltd. is a giant real estate firm located at Santacruz Mumbai. I worked in its IT department.

Responsibilities

- Gathering requirements from business people, providing best possible solution using SharePoint and other Microsoft technologies.
- Maintaining SharePoint 2013 server, Managing solutions and supporting different live application running on SharePoint
- Integrating SharePoint with SAP and Salesforce by collaborating with different teams
- Creating and Maintaining documentation throughout the application development

Contact: Krishna Menon - +919930253389

SharePoint Consultant i2e Consulting Pvt Ltd.

03/2016 - 02/2017

Mumbai

i2e Consulting is a global software services company. I worked as contracted resources there under contract with Ashapura SoftTech Ltd.

- Actively participate in client meetings and Requirement analysis, Design and Development of responsive Intranet on SharePoint using Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Jquery.
- Updating clients with daily and weekly status reports
- Designing master pages & page layouts from PSD images
- Create interactive animated dashboards & image dashboards using Jquery
- Provide training to the client for Content Management and Branding

Contact: Sharad Pawar - +919820273261

EDUCATION

05/2011 - 05/2015

Bachelors of Engineering Gujarat Technological University

Ahmedabad

SKILLS

Microsoft SharePoint .Net Office 365 C# MVC WebAPI SharePoint PnP Jquery JSOM/CSOM/REST API Bootstrap HTML/CSS Web Development/Designing

PROJECTS

Project Workspace (SharePoint-Salesforce integration) (02/2017 - 06/2017)

- Main Aim of this project is to create a project workspace for sales department, where they can collaborate, share, manage documents as well as user permissions. My main task is to provide a simple user interface so that non-tech users can use the project workspace with
- Developed a REST API which is hosted inside a SharePoint Web Application to integrate with Salesforce

Action Tracker-Personal Business Application (08/2016 – 02/2017)

- The project objective is to facilitate a user from Pfizer to track & customize meetings created by colleagues on his shared outlook calendar in SharePoint site. It is one stop solution where the user can create, update & customize meetings, meeting agendas & meeting action items

WRD External Partnering Information & Communication (03/2016 - 02/2017)

- The project objective is to facilitate users to have a glance of the latest updates of Pfizer's External Partnering information using interactive Animated Dashboards, News/Blogs, and News Letters
- SharePoint branding using custom master page & page layouts made by Bootstrap and Jquery from PSD images
- Create interactive animated dashboards & image dashboards
- Create custom Site column, Content Types & List definition
- Designing workflows to send a notification to app user for new deals added to the site based on individual user interests

Dubai Sports World (03/2015 - 03/2016)

The project objective is to facilitate users / anonymous visitors to have a glance of the latest updates of Dubai Sports world.

LANGUAGES

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Gujarati

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Reading **Tech Trends**

Learning to play Guitar

SharePoint

Javascript technologies

Angular.IO